Excuse me, sir. Sir, question
for you. Is this your yacht?
No, no, it's my friend's.
This is your yacht?
Yeah, how can I help you?
I go all over the
world interviewing the most successful people.
I grew a channel to 10 million followers.
Do you think I could interview you real quick?
About what?
What did you do to
be able to afford a yacht?
I'm in the oil, the oil industry.
Are you a business owner?
I am.
How long have you been a business owner?
Oh my gosh, well, I'm no longer really
a business owner. I sold it in 2023.
You sold your company?
I sold my company, yeah.
For how much?
For me, my equity shares were worth about $90 million.
$90 million?
Yeah.
Are you a billionaire?
Yes.
You're a billionaire?
Yes, I am.
Are you actually?
Yes.
That's incredible.
What do you do differently?
Like, what do you do differently for millionaires?
That's what I want to know.
There are over 360 female billionaires in the entire world.
So I flew out to one of the richest
cities in the world, Miami, Florida, to come find
and ask a woman who built multi-billion
dollar and multi-million dollar empires out here
to figure out how they created their wealth and
how you can do the exact same thing to
become financially free in 2020.
So stay tuned with us from start to
finish because this video is going to be crazy.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
We're right now at one of
the wealthiest parts in Miami at YOLO.
We got a G-Wagon pulling
up to the valet right now.
We got to see if we can go
get some data from the back here, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yes.
Sorry.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yes.
And what do you do for living out here
in Miami to be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I'm in the oil industry.
You're in the oil business?
Yes, oil business.
Are you a business owner?
I am.
How long have you been a business owner?
For like 16 years.
Over these 16 years across your companies,
what's the most amount of money you've made
in a single year?
I don't know if I should say that.
You can be arranged revenue, not personal revenue.
Between six to seven million.
Seven million dollars.
Yes, seven million dollars.
So you're a millionaire.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And then I go all over the
world interviewing the world's most successful people.
One quick minute with you for our channel real quick.
Sure.
Is that okay?
After this.
Yes, one second.
Awesome.
What is the best financial advice that you've ever received?
Well-behaved women rarely make history.
Women who play by the
rules, they won't really get anywhere.
You got to break the rules.
Now you're in the oil business.
I am.
What business has made you the most money?
I think manufacturing solar panels.
Manufacturing solar panels and I think pumping crude oil.
What's the biggest deal you've ever closed?
It was like a $20 million deal.
$20 million?
Yeah, it was a $28 million deal.
$28 million?
$28 million deal, but I got commissioned.
It wasn't my deal, but
I did it in Puerto Rico.
I did it in the
airport and the commission was hefty.
In the oil business or what was that?
In the oil business and I was 21.
Are you a buyer or a seller?
I feel like I'm both, depending on
what the market is, but I'm a seller.
I sell, sell, sell.
Are you good at sales?
I can sell water too.
A fish.
Well, I've been selling for years.
I've been selling for years and I was in
corporate customer service for 10 years, so I know how
to deal with people.
What's your secret to selling?
You're not asking the wrong
questions, you're asking the wrong person.
That's game right there.
Yeah, keep asking, keep asking, keep asking, keep asking.
Go get a loan, sign up
for whatever, close mobs don't get fed.
And don't be afraid.
Just go.
If you don't go to the banks, if you
don't try and find lenders, you're not going to
know what you need.
So you weren't afraid to borrow money from banks?
No, I borrow money all the time.
Actually.
I do.
How do you leverage that debt into wealth though?
I spread it out.
I spread it out and I multiply it.
A lot of the times you say, okay, this
is where we're going to spend it, but I budget
it and I spread it out and a lot of the
times I pay it back before it even makes what it
needs to make.
So if you lost everything tomorrow,
could you make it all back?
Absolutely.
I can make it in 10 phone calls.
So your network's important?
My network is hefty.
Big players.
Have you ever met a billionaire?
I've dated billionaires.
You've dated billionaires?
Of course.
What have you learned from all the
billionaires that you've met, that you've interacted with
at your network?
What do billionaires do differently from everybody else?
I think that more than anything, they like to talk.
They like quality time.
They like listeners.
They like listeners and they can
separate the doers from the non-doers.
You're going to be a student
for life and be open to that.
It doesn't matter where you are.
I'm constantly learning and I'm going
to learn until my last breath.
So billionaires, they love that.
It's the playground and you got to take notes.
You got to file taxes like a billionaire.
You got to be a big girl.
Have you filed taxes like a billionaire?
Always.
All the time.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So do you pay a lot in taxes?
I mean, I have several trust accounts.
So what's the best way to
not pay a lot of taxes?
Because the wealthiest people I've
met, they don't pay any taxes.
I would say knowing how to do business, knowing
how to write off, and then of course, actually
securing your wealth.
And I want to say making sure that
you have that generational wealth by having trust accounts,
by having certain portfolios and filing
it properly, doing business properly and knowing
exactly how you can write off.
You really have to have a really good
financial advisor and have a really crazy financial
team.
Your team has to be hardcore.
Invest in it.
Invest.
Invest in.
Because the more you invest in the best
financial advisors and the best tax attorneys, you're
going to save a lot of money.
Like when you build a team in every
single part of your business, when you build the
right team, they make money for you.
In your sleep, you can trust everybody.
I think your team.
Invest in your team.
So we got her coming out of the G-Wagon,
out the valet, and she is in, of all businesses,
the oil business.
You guys, if that puts anything in perspective,
I want you guys to realize how much money
is really out there in this world to
be made, no matter what industry you are in.
Whether it's tech, finance, real estate, oil,
energy, you never know how people are
making their money.
Great interview out here in Miami.
We got to keep this one rolling
and go get another one, you guys.
Come on.
Let's go.
All right, you guys.
So we just got to our destination at the
design district, and we got somebody who pulled up
in a baby blue Bentley.
I have never seen this car before, but we're
going to go up, try and get an interview with
them, see if we can get some give with
them and how they got into Bentley in today's world.
Man, this is a crazy whip right here.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am.
Question for you.
Yeah.
Is this your Bentley?
Yes, it is.
And what do you do for living out here
in Miami to be able to afford a Bentley?
I'm an entrepreneur, an investor.
How long have you been a business owner?
Oh, my gosh.
Well, I'm no longer really a business owner.
I sold it in 2023.
You sold your company?
I sold my company, yeah.
How much?
For me, my equity shares were worth about $90 million.
$90 billion?
Yeah.
So how much was the total company sold for?
Well, the company was valued at
the time a little over $300 million.
$300 billion?
Yeah.
And I go all over the world, and
you're one of the most successful business owners.
Could I get one quick minute
with you for the channel real quick?
Of course.
You got it.
Well, I owned Solidcore for almost
10 years before I sold it.
What investment made you the most money?
Solidcore.
I mean, I put $175 grand into Solidcore,
and it turned into $100 million in 10 years.
So in other words, putting the money
back into the business and investing in yourself
is the best thing to sell?
Oh, my God.
I would bet on myself
every day and twice on Sunday.
Like, there is no better bet than me because
I know I'm going to win, and if I'm passionate
about something, I'm going to give everything I got.
Now, I'm a little bit more in wealth preservation mode.
So the money that I made,
I want to continue to make money.
That's why I'm an investor.
I'm an investor in startups.
I have money in private equity and hedge funds.
In the stock market, I do loans.
You know, I'm very diversified now.
But I think for entrepreneurs, if you think
you have the special sauce, you've got to
go all in on yourself.
I love that.
Did you have a lot of people that hated
on you or doubted you when you were building
your business?
I mean, I'm a woman who's been very successful.
Of course, I've had other
people who has hated on me.
It's just part of the process.
So the way that I deal with that is
I just try to empower as many women as possible.
So how did you personally find that self-belief
to go generate millions and millions of dollars?
Yeah.
Because a lot of people go down.
When they start out, they kind of
get worried about people saying stuff about them.
They're going out of the box.
How did you find the
self-belief to make millions of dollars?
You just have to not care, you know?
And the things that I was building, I
was building a company that was making people's
lives happier and healthier.
So I was excited every single day.
There was nothing that was going to get in
the way of me building an empire across the
country that I thought was improving people's lives.
And normally, the people that have something
to say about that are people who normally
sit on the sidelines and aren't actually doing the work.
So why would I care
what they have to say anyway?
Yeah.
They're watching from the bleachers.
They're not actually in the game.
Yeah.
Exactly.
And you know, the cheap seats
are called cheap seats for a reason.
Wow.
I love that.
That's gay right there.
Are you a reader by any chance?
Yes.
How many books have you read?
All over my lifetime?
Oh my gosh.
I don't know if I can even do that math.
A lot.
Yeah.
What was the number one book that changed your life?
Oh my gosh.
The number one book that I read every
few years is what I've already mentioned, and
it's How to Win Friends
and Influence People by Dale Carnegie.
It is simple.
It is effective.
And it's one of the reasons
we started using names at Solidcore.
So if you've ever been to a Solidcore class,
you hear your name over and over again.
Why?
Because your name is the most
important word to you in any language.
So I wanted to make sure
that you felt seen, at home, respected,
and it makes you want to come back
into an environment that you feel that way.
What's the deepest life quote that you've ever heard?
Easy choices, hard life.
Hard choices, easy life.
Listen, I think a lot
of people think after selling Solidcore,
I'm gallivanting around and doing whatever.
I am up pretty much
every day by 5.30, 6 a.m.
I am at the gym six days a week.
I play beach volleyball for two
to three hours, five days a week.
I cook my own food.
You know, I'm...
I'm as disciplined as they come
because I want to be as healthy
and as active for as long as possible.
And if I make decisions
that aren't in support of that,
I'm going to have a difficult
time in my 50s, 60s, and 70s.
So I choose to make the hard decision now
to continue to make sure my life
stays as easy and comfortable as possible.
It reminds me of this saying,
the road to heaven often feels like hell,
and the road to hell often feels like heaven.
Yeah, you know?
And like, make decisions today that
make you proud of yourself today
and make you proud of yourself tomorrow.
So like, if you're going to
go out drinking all day today,
you might feel fun and good in the moment,
but guess what happens the next day?
You feel like shit.
You have low energy.
I just don't put myself in those situations.
So was it all worth it?
Was the sacrifice to build
a, you know, $100 million company,
was it all worth it?
Oh my, I didn't feel like I sacrificed anything.
I loved every part of it.
I learned so much.
My team was amazing.
And I got to build a company that helped people
create the strongest version of themselves.
Like, I would do it all again in a heartbeat.
You got amazing advice.
Thanks.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
Have a great day.
You guys, this video has been incredible so far.
We're headed right now to go get
our next interview out here in Miami.
But before we do that,
I have a very quick, very important announcement to make.
So a couple months ago, I
launched and built what has become
one of the greatest and biggest entrepreneur communities
in the entire world.
And school just announced that our community
is the number one in the world
for business, money, and entrepreneurship.
What's even crazier than that
is you can join the community for free today.
And the reason why we became the number one community
for business owners is because every single week,
I bring in the biggest business owners in the world,
even billionaires, to directly mentor you,
the members that join the community.
All right.
So I'm live calls that
I host every single week inside
where you can ask your questions directly to the people
that I'm interviewing.
So no matter what business,
no matter what industry you're in,
if you want to learn how to invest,
to make your money multiply,
how to sell or negotiate like a millionaire or billionaire,
how to start and scale that business,
how to get out of that nine to five,
no matter what industry, like I said,
you're in no matter what point in your business,
we've got millionaires that are members in the community,
people that have built seven, eight figure businesses,
six figure businesses.
So come join a network of like-minded entrepreneurs
and come get mentored.
And from the world's most successful people
to join for free today,
go down to the link
in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you on the inside,
inside of the school of mentors,
the number one community in the world.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Guys, we just got to a
yacht Marina out here in Fort Lauderdale,
another super wealthy area in Miami.
We're going to be asking yacht owners what they did
to be able to afford yachts out here
and how you can do the exact same thing.
Sir, is this your yacht?
No, no, no.
I just drive the bus.
You drive the bus.
Thank you, brother.
I appreciate you.
All right.
So let's see what we can do, man.
Oh, for one, all we
can do is keep on going
because everyone knows a step closer to a yes.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, question for you.
Is this your yacht?
No, no, it's my friend's.
This is your yacht?
Yeah, how can I help you?
I go all over the world
interviewing the most successful people.
I grew a channel to 10 million followers.
Do you think I could interview you real quick?
About what?
What did you do to
be able to afford a yacht?
Oh, I'm actually in the beauty industry.
You're in the beauty industry?
Yes, I own a professional hair and hair brand worldwide.
How long have you been a business owner?
Well, I mean, I've been
in the beauty industry 42 years
and my very first business was in the beauty industry.
My first business was a four-foot little square
that I used to do hair on,
so I've always been 1099 and independent in person.
Over these 42 years across your company,
what was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Oh, for nine figures.
Nine figures?
In one year.
In one year?
Could I interview you real quick?
Sure.
Is that okay?
Come aboard.
How you doing, man?
Appreciate you guys.
Thank you.
So if you've never been on a yacht before,
you gotta take your shoes off up here.
Thank you so much for having us on.
No problem.
We appreciate that.
Thanks for coming aboard.
Are you a billionaire?
Yes.
You're a billionaire?
Yes, I am.
Are you actually?
Yes.
That's incredible.
What do you do differently for millionaires?
That's what I wanna know.
I'm addicted.
I love, love being an entrepreneur.
I'm actually a serial entrepreneur.
I have 15 companies.
So it just starts compounding and, you know.
It's a game.
It's a game and I'm addicted and some people say,
oh, but like now you can afford leisure.
Well, what's leisure?
I don't, what is leisure to people?
Leisure to me is really
getting to do what I love,
getting to share it with people I love
and obviously giving back.
So that's my leisure.
Which is building for you.
Yes, it is.
And have you ever been broke before?
I have, many times.
Our first company completely failed.
We lost everything and then started It's a 10
with only one bottle
because we couldn't afford anything else.
And I was in that business with It's a 10
for 10 years with a partner
and I bought my partner out.
I'm the only Latina female brand
in the world of my size
that's 100% owned by the original owner, the founder.
How many Latina billionaires are there?
You know, that's a good question.
I don't really know.
Probably not many.
Yeah.
Not many, especially self-made ones.
When you were coming up, when you were growing,
when you were building your business,
how did you know you made it?
I was actually in New York City
and we had just had a few products out
and I went in the airport
and there was a salon in there
and I walked up to the girl behind the counter
and asked her, do you carry It's a 10?
And she's like, I can't believe you're asking me that.
And I'm thinking to myself, why?
I mean, you're a salon.
She said, because we just sold our last bottle
and we're actually, I'm not going to say it,
another brand's salon
and we aren't supposed to be carrying It's a 10.
But I told my manager
we had to get it in
and we can't keep it in.
It's all off the shelves.
And I just love the stuff.
And I said, oh, wow.
Glad to hear that.
I actually created that company.
And she said, can I hug you?
I always said I was going to hug the person
who ever created It's a 10.
So she ran around the corner
and gave me a big hug.
And you know, when you find that passion,
organic passion behind a brand
and you become a worldwide brand
built on that organic passion,
it's priceless to me.
That's a beautiful story.
Thank you.
What's your last message to the younger generation?
How can somebody become a billionaire in 2025?
It's not what you have.
It's what you do with what you have.
And a lot of people say, oh yeah,
I don't work harder.
I work smarter.
It's not about even working.
It's about being smarter.
It's about being more strategic.
Go where they don't go
because it's a tough market out there.
But if you can bring innovation
or something different to it,
so zig when they zag
and literally get creative
and have fun while you're doing it
because you know what?
It goes fast.
I've been doing this my whole life
and you'd really have to sometimes
just enjoy the moment.
It's a great ride.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
Guys, this video was incredible to make,
but I need you guys to do me a favor
to like and subscribe for amazing content
I've got coming every single week.
Because I'm going all over the world
to find and ask the most successful people
their advice to you
to become wealthy and financially free
in today's world.
And if you are not a member yet,
you need to right now
go join my private entrepreneur community
for free today.
Come try it out.
Come get mentored directly from the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview.
That's what we do inside the community.
Every week I'm hosting live calls
to bring the most successful business owners in
to directly mentor you
and answer every question that you have.
So go join the community
by going down to the link
in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you
on the inside of these
school of mentors,
the number one entrepreneur community
in the world.
With that being said,
I'll see you in the next video.